
const data = [
  {
    question: "Cat : Kitten :: Dog : ?",
    option1: "Cub",
    option2: "Calf",
    option3: "Puppy",
    option4: "Foal",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Apple, Banana, Mango, Potato ?",
    option1: "Apple",
    option2: "Banana",
    option3: "Mango",
    option4: "Potato",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
     
    question: "2, 4, 8, 16, ?",
    option1: "18",
    option2: "24",
    option3: "30",
     option4:"32",
    ans: 4,
  },

  {
    id: 4,
    question:"If CAT is written as DBU, how is DOG written?",
    option1: "EPH",
    option2: "EOG",
    option3: "FPH",
    option4: "DNH",
    ans: 1,
  },

  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Ram is the brother of Sita. Sita is the mother of Aman. How is Ram related to Aman?",
    option1: "Father",
    option2: "Uncle",
    option3: "Brother",
    option4: "Grandfather",
    ans: 2,
  },

  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Rahul walks 10 m east and then 5 m north. How far is he from the starting point?",
    option1: "15 m",
    option2: "10 m",
    option3: "12 m",
    option4: "11.18 m",
    ans: 4,
  },

  {
    id: 7,
    question: "In a class of 20 students, Ravi is 5th from the top. What is his rank from the bottom?",
    option1:"14",
    option2:"15",
    option3: "16",
    option4:"17",
    ans: 3,
  },

  {
     
    question: " Pen, Pencil, Eraser, Book",
    option1: "Pen",
    option2: "Pencil",
    option3: "Eraser",
    option4: "Book",
    ans: 4,
  },

  {
    
    question: "A, D, G, J, ?",
    option1:"K",
    option2: "L",
    option3:"M",
    option4: "N",
    ans: 3,
  },

  {
    
    question: "Statement: All dogs are animals./Conclusion: All animals are dogs.",
    option1:"True",
    option2: "False",
    option3: "Both true",
    option4: "Both false",
    ans: 2,
  },

  {
     
    question: "If 5 + 3 = 28 and 7 + 2 = 63, then 6 + 4 = ?",
    option1: "40",
    option2: "50",
    option3: "60",
    option4: "70",
    ans: 3,
  },

  {
  
    question: "What is the angle between the hands of a clock at 3:00?",
     option1: "60째",
     option2: "90째",
     option3: "120째",
     option4: "180째",
    ans: 2,
  },
];

export default data;

